>> 扬声器 1: 在编译时，我有一个有关函数的问题
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: I have a question about
the function when the compilation is
在你说的大理石上，其他阶级的功能会得到它的内容吗 ?
happening, the function other class gets
its contents in the marble did you say?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不确定我是否在关注
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm
not sure I'm following.
>> 扬声器 1: 因此当正在编译其他类时 -
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
when other class is being compiled-
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有一张地图，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There's a map,
就像一个计划，比如一个由编译器提出来的一个路线图，
like a plan, like a roadmap,
made up by the compiler to say, for
那个蓝色的水桶你要创建一个叫老师的标识。
that blue bucket, you need to create
an identifier called teacher.
>> 演讲者 1: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Okay.
>> Kyle Simpson: 是的，这就是编译器输出的基本计划
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, that's what
compiler outputs is basically a plan for
范围。
that scope.
>> 演讲者 1: 那么目标部分何时发生?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
when does the targeting part happen?
>> Kyle Simpson: 那是在运行时，这是我们现在的阶段。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's at run time,
which is the stage we're in now.
在运行时，当从某个变量中抽取该 otherClass 函数时，
At run time, when that otherClass
function is pulled from some variable,
就像在 13 线上
like it is on line 13, and
它已经被处死了现在我们知道有一个完整的计划要做这个蓝色的水桶
it's executed, well now we know there's
a whole plan to make this blue bucket.
所以让我们先把整个蓝色的水桶和所有弹珠一起
So let's go first make the whole blue
bucket with all the marbles, and
现在我们已经开始运作了
now we're in it and we're running it.
当我们跨越第四线
And when we run across line four,
目标位置有个叫老师的大理石
there's a marble called teacher
in the target position.
所以我们发现目标位置和目标位置
So we discover the source
versus target position
在编译时，但在运行时间之前，我们不使用该信息。
at compile time, but we don't use
that information until run time.
有什么帮助吗
Does that help?
>> 演讲者 1: 对，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yep, thank you.
>> 扬声器 3: 所以它本质上创建了一个占位符吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So
it creates a place holder essentially?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，基本上就像一个藏宝图，对。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, basically think
of it like a treasure map, right.
有一张地图，有一个计划，就像是要为每个范围做一个清单，
There's a map, there's a plan,
it's like a to do list for every scope,
这就是编译器输出的内容这是可执行的代码
that's what compiler outputs,
that's the executable code.
当它运行的时候，它实际上是存在的。
And then when it runs is when it
all actually comes into existence.
嗯。 >> 扬声器 4: 还有一个问题。
Yeah.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: One more question.
当我们进入该功能的范围时，我的意思是如果我们输入
When we enter the scope of that function,
I mean if we enter
多次重新设置值和内容的过程。
multiple times, there's another process
that resets the values and things.
你知道我在说什么吗
How does that work,
you know what I'm saying?
>> Kyle Simpson: 每次执行函数时，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Every time
you execute a function,
从零开始重新创建环境。
the environment is recreated from scratch.
>> 演讲者 4: 好的，这到底是什么呢 ? 在编译器里吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay, so what does that
actually, is it like in the compiler?
我不知道我不知道
I don't know.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 记住，编译器只为桶做一个计划，它说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So remember, the compiler
only makes a plan for the bucket, it says,
哎，只要你需要绿色的水桶，这就是绿色水桶应该看的
hey whenever you need a green bucket, this
is what the green bucket ought to look
就像它的内容应该是这样但是它还不存在
like, and this is what it's contents ought
to be, but it doesn't actually exist yet.
然后，每当您执行绿色存储区时，该计划就会被实现到内存中。
And then every time you execute the green
bucket, that plan is effected into memory.
然后当绿色水桶完成那个计划的时候所有东西都消失了
And then when the green bucket finishes
that plan, all that stuff goes away, and
那么下次你来管理它的时候，它就会再从这个计划中产生它，好的。
then the next time you run it,
it creates it from the plan again, okay.
所以编译器输出实际上不是保留内存，是
So the compiler output is not actually
reserved memory, it's the plan for
如何保留记忆和制作弹珠
how to reserve memory and
make marbles and all that.